hi Steve and welcome to another
您好史蒂夫，欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips and this
Spring 技巧的分期付款和这个
installment we're gonna look at the
分期付款，我们将看看
reactor based Cloud Foundry Java client
基于反应堆的Cloud Foundry Java客户端
version 3.3 whatever - you know - at
3.3版本-无论您知道-在
that point so 3.3 X this reactor based
那一点，所以这个反应堆的3.3 X
client is very interesting to me it
客户对我来说很有趣
provides you the ability to talk to the
使您能够与
Cloud Foundry API which in turn lets you
Cloud Foundry API，可让您
write programs that work with a client
编写与客户一起使用的程序
under API to do all sorts all the sorts
在API下做所有各种各样的事情
of things that clarinha can do there's a
clarinha可以做的事情有一个
lot of reasons why you might do this
您可能会这样做的很多原因
right the the the the common reason is
正确的常见原因是
because you want to control or interact
因为你想控制或互动
with the platform to manipulate all the
用平台来操纵所有
things that it allows you to to control
它可以让您控制的事物
programmatically right well and one
以编程的方式很好，一个
great reason or justification for this
有充分的理由或理由
is when you read the continuous delivery
当您阅读持续交付时
book with them they Farley and just
和他们一起预定法利，
humble the continuous that the delivery
谦虚的连续交付
book talks about having one kind of one
书中谈到一种
kind of tool one tool for every
一种工具每一种工具
environment one application that it can
环境它可以的一个应用程序
deploy everything right so a lot of us
正确部署所有东西
will typically write that kind of code
通常会写那种代码
you can't see it but I'm using giant
你看不到，但我在用巨人
dripping air quotes here a lot people
空气报价滴在这里很多人
use that code well the way that code
很好地使用该代码
using bash write and bash isn't really
使用bash write和bash并不是真的
all that flexible and it can be slow
这么灵活，可能会很慢
right so if you're using the cloud
对，所以如果您使用云
funding Java client with with with bash
通过bash与Java客户一起融资
that's certainly workable but you you
那当然是可行的，但是你你
lose the ability to test it you lose the
失去测试的能力，就失去了
ability to interact with that code and
与该代码进行交互的能力，以及
to refactor into to sort of scale it out
重构成某种程度的扩展
bash becomes very hard to scale after a
bash变得很难扩展
certain point even with functions and so
甚至具有功能的特定点
on so fascism not going to get you very
如此法西斯主义不会让你非常
far and you do need to use bash right as
远，您确实需要使用bash作为
much Sun I wish it were otherwise Cloud
我希望太阳多了否则云
Foundry requires you to run some
铸造厂需要您运行一些
commands before you can do a CF push
在执行CF推送之前先执行命令
with a manifest right you might for
具有明显的权利，你可能会
example require that your application be
示例要求您的应用程序是
bound to a my sequel instance or to a
绑定到我的续集实例或
you know to a key value store or
您知道键值存储或
whatever whatever your backing services
不管您的支持服务是什么
there's no way to declaratively say in a
没有办法在
manifest I need Cloud Foundry to please
清单我需要Cloud Foundry请
create this instance of this backing
创建此后备实例
service and then in the same manifest
服务，然后在同一清单中
stipulated of that backing service
该支持服务规定的
should be bound to the application you
应该绑定到您的应用程序
can specify the latter bit you can say
可以指定您可以说的后一点
that I have a backing service that's
我有一个支持服务
already
已经
created out there somewhere by whoever
由任何人在那里创建
knows what and I want to be I want to
知道什么，我想成为我想
bind this application to that but you do
将此应用程序绑定到该应用程序，但是您可以
have to create that application
必须创建该应用程序
somewhere so if nothing else your your
某处，所以如果没有别的你
CF push just became to command to the CF
CF推送刚刚成为对CF的命令
create service and then your specifying
创建服务，然后指定
the the service name and the instance
服务名称和实例
type and I would rather the plan type
类型，我宁愿计划类型
and then the instance name for that
然后是该实例的名称
service and then your binding that into
服务，然后将其绑定到
the application and if you want to do
该应用程序，如果你想做
anything more complicated you just want
您只想做的更复杂的事情
to check the stage if you want to see if
检查舞台是否要看
an applications already deployed maybe
已经部署的应用程序
you don't want to create the service if
您不想创建服务，如果
it's already created for example you
它已经创建了，例如你
want to do you want to avoid that if you
想做，如果你想避免
want to deploy service brokers if want
想要部署服务代理
to deploy custom routes all of this gets
部署自定义路线，所有这些
to be a little painful with bash
对bash有点痛苦
right so we while I like bash I don't
对，所以我们虽然我喜欢bash但我不喜欢
believe we should spend as much I don't
相信我们应该花我不多的钱
believe you should spend a lot of time
相信你应该花很多时间
especially associated with business
特别是与业务有关
logic that we care very much about in
我们非常关注的逻辑
bash and so we want one kind of
bash，所以我们想要一种
application one kind of thing that we
应用一种我们所需要的东西
can use to deploy that's the same
可以用来部署相同的
working software from every environment
各种环境下的工作软件
right across every environment this is
在每个环境中
one of the key tenants and contains
主要租户之一，包含
delivery it's that everything that that
交付就是那一切
that executes everything that that is
执行所有的
required to recreate the state of your
需要重新创建您的状态
system should be version controlled
系统应受版本控制
including the the configuration and the
包括配置和
the sort of creation of the environments
环境的创造
themselves so in when the book was
他们自己，当书是
written that meant that perhaps the
写的意思是也许
assets in a virtual machine reversion
虚拟机还原中的资产
controlled or virtual maybe they may be
控制的还是虚拟的，也许他们可能是
maybe even the virtual machine itself
甚至虚拟机本身
these days we don't need to go that farm
这些天我们不需要去那个农场
we can assume given a plain vanilla sort
我们可以假设给定一个普通的香草排序
of cloud funding installation that we
我们的云资金安装
can take our application and the binary
可以接受我们的应用程序和二进制文件
that you know was created by building
你知道是由建筑创造的
the application and apply under manifest
申请并根据清单申请
and whatever and get to a reproducible
和任何东西，并获得可复制
result but still having that recipe go
结果，但仍然有食谱
beyond the manifest is interesting and
超越清单是有趣的，
we don't wanna do it in bash so this is
我们不想用bash来做，所以这是
one thing that's really nice about the
一件事真的很好
the Cloud Foundry Java client is that
Cloud Foundry Java客户端是
you get to you get the ability to really
你得到你有能力真正
interact with the API and you can use a
与API进行交互，您可以使用
compiler to guide you in and what is
编译器指导您，什么是
correct and what is not correct you get
正确，什么不正确，你得到
more feedback the other thing is that if
更多的反馈是，如果
you're using the reactive API if you're
如果您正在使用反应式API
using the reactive content of Java
使用Java的反应式内容
client it can do things frankly far more
客户它可以做更多坦率的事情
efficiently and then the command-line
然后是命令行
client can do remember the command-line
客户端可以记住命令行
client
客户
is written in procedurally correct go
以程序正确的方式编写
language code you're you are to issue
您要发布的语言代码
one command after the other so you issue
一个命令接一个命令，所以您发出
the first command and then the second
第一个命令，然后第二个
and then the third and so and so on and
然后是第三个，依此类推，
if there is any inefficiency in the
如果效率低下
first command well that's too bad right
第一个命令很好，太糟糕了吧
the second command will have to wait
第二个命令将不得不等待
until the first one is done there is no
直到第一个完成
opportunity to take advantage for
利用机会
example of the idleness so that things
闲事的例子
that are successive or rather than that
是连续的，或者不是
could be made concurrent are concurrent
可以使并发成为并发
right there's no pipelining in effect
正确没有流水线
and so we have the ability to take a
所以我们有能力接受
manage that pipelining because the card
管理流水线，因为卡
from the Java client is based on project
来自Java客户端的基于项目
reactor which as you no doubt at this
你对此毫无疑问的反应堆
point know underpins Spring Framework
要点是Spring Framework 的基础
fives reactive story in particular it
法式反应性故事尤其如此
underpins the spring Webb flux Webber
支撑了Webb的Webb通量Webber
runtime so we want to take advantage of
运行时，所以我们想利用
the efficiencies of building reactive
反应式建筑的效率
code and remember a lot of what we're
编码并记住很多我们所要做的
doing here when we deploy applications
部署应用程序时在这里做
is i/o so this is perfect for that right
是I / O，所以这是完美的选择
a reactor and reactive programming in
反应堆和反应式编程
general are ideal for i/o sensitive and
一般是I / O敏感和
i/o driven what code another thing that
我驱动了什么代码另一件事
I really like about using the Java
我真的很喜欢使用Java
client here the reactive Cloud Foundry
这里的客户是反应式Cloud Foundry
Java client is that it does in that sort
Java客户端就是那样做的
of continues that every you know spirit
继续，每个您知道的精神
it does give us one recipe that we can
它确实给了我们一个配方，我们可以
use to deploy the application across
用于跨多个应用程序的部署
your environment and in a sense it's an
您的环境，从某种意义上讲，
installer script right it's an install
安装脚本正确的是安装
that exe if you want to it's a program
该exe文件，如果你想它是一个程序
that we can use to deploy the
我们可以用来部署
application itself that logic could
应用本身，逻辑可以
actually be in the application itself
实际上在应用程序本身中
imagine that you have and you have logic
想象你拥有逻辑
in the codebase itself that deploys
在部署的代码库本身中
itself you can just say you can point it
本身，你可以说可以指出
at whatever you know cloud machinery you
无论您知道什么云机器，
want and say deploy yourself and you
想要并说出部署自己和你
know who better to deploy the system
知道谁更好地部署系统
then the software itself right this is
那么软件本身就是
this is very different from the old sort
这与旧的分类有很大的不同
of cots model where you have something
婴儿床模型的地方，你有东西
off the shelf and if it's a cloud-based
现成的，如果它是基于云的
thing if it's a distributed system then
如果是分布式系统的话
it gets very painful to figure out how
弄清楚如何
to deploy it this this is actually going
部署它，这实际上是要
to deploy itself all it needs is
部署自身所需的一切是
familiar footing so it's a much more
熟悉的基础，所以还有更多
professional feel and specifically
专业的感觉，特别是
there's no chance of there's
没有机会
chance of somebody downstream getting it
下游有人得到它的机会
wrong because they're gonna just use the
错误的，因为他们只会使用
exact same install script or sixth
完全相同的安装脚本或第六个
install program as you would I saw a
就像我看到的那样安装程序
great talk by Kelsey Hightower and he
Kelsey Hightower的精彩演讲，他
was talking about this idea he's talking
在谈论他在说这个想法
about what he called self deploying
关于他所谓的自我部署
applications and he he doped that bash
应用程序，他他掺杂了重击
he took that bash is the reason people
他认为这是人们的原因
leave IT and I think he's got a great
离开IT，我认为他的表现很棒
point there and he talked about having
指向那里，他谈到
commands in your application they would
在您的应用程序中的命令
actually hoist you know your application
实际提升您知道您的应用程序
onto a cloud platform in his case he was
在他的情况下到一个云平台上
talking about kubernetes which is
谈论kubernetes是
certainly an option as well but I think
当然也是一种选择，但我认为
it applies to just anything and anything
它适用于任何事物
cloud-based that has an API of course
基于云的，当然有一个API
and content is a great great option here
内容是这里的绝佳选择
because you don't need anything more
因为你不需要更多了
than the binary of the codebase itself
比代码库本身的二进制文件
in order for this to work whereas with
为了这个工作而
the communities you need a container or
您需要一个容器的社区或
something right so this is actually an
正确的事情，所以这实际上是
ideal opportunity for us so we're gonna
对我们来说是一个理想的机会，所以我们要
go ahead and demonstrate the reactive
继续演示反应性
cloud vendor client and look at how it
云供应商客户端，看看它如何
allows us to work with the API now my my
现在允许我使用API
friend Kenny Bustani and I we were to
朋友肯尼·布斯塔尼（Kenny Bustani）和我
book called cloud native Java and that
这本书叫做云原生Java，
in the book we we have integration tests
在书中，我们有集成测试
and those integration tests all are
这些集成测试都是
driven using the reactive API right the
使用反应式API驱动
reactive cloud for new Java client right
适用于新Java客户端权利的反应性云
the the API allows us to the client
API允许我们提供给客户
liaos us to exist you know sort of smoke
聊聊我们的存在，你知道那种烟
test in to end test our chat our
测试结束测试我们的聊天我们
chapters the examples in the chapters so
章节中的示例
I think that experience has been very
我认为经验非常
very useful for us because we we saw how
对我们非常有用，因为我们看到了
to compose all these different things
组成所有这些不同的东西
and how to deploy working applications
以及如何部署有效的应用程序
you know with confidence that we'd get
你充满信心地知道我们会
the right result and it was also faster
正确的结果，而且速度更快
like I said we because we're using their
就像我说的，因为我们正在使用他们的
back to the API were able to go faster
回到API能够更快
than that we could if we had written the
比起我们写的
equivalent commands using the the Cloud
使用云的等效命令
Foundry CF client and a bash script it
Foundry CF客户端和bash脚本
was actually much faster in some cases
实际上在某些情况下要快得多
because we could take advantage of
因为我们可以利用
concurrency and so on
并发等等
so let's take advantage of this go ahead
因此，让我们利用这一优势继续前进
and you know go to start out spring
你知道去 Spring 开始
today I will build an application here
今天我将在这里构建一个应用程序
we're gonna use spring boot to that om7
我们将使用 spring boot 到该om7
and we're you we're going to use some
而我们是您，我们将使用一些
auto configuration for the
自动配置
clarify new Java client now this
现在澄清新的Java客户端
auto-configuration has it yet found a
自动配置尚未找到
steady home right this is a actually a
稳定的房屋权利，这实际上是一个
pull request that is the outstanding
拉请求是优秀的
right now I think it's going to land in
现在我认为它将降落在
the spring cloud cloud foundry module as
Spring Cloud云代工模块为
a sort of module inside that it'll be an
里面的一种模块
artifact in the inside of there so you
在里面的神器，所以你
can just you know you'll be able to
只要你知道你就能
bring in spring cloud Finchley this is
带来Spring Cloud Finchley，这是
probably where that would live in spring
可能会在 Spring 住
cloud Finchley which is the the version
云芬奇利是哪个版本
of spring cloud that will be based on
Spring 的云将基于
spring boot to that o which itself will
spring boot 到本身会
land in the first few months of 2018 so
在2018年前几个月登陆
this will be you know in spring cut
这将是您在春季切工中知道的
eventually which will succeed spring
最终 Spring 会成功
boot to that oh so we're talking about a
引导到那个哦，所以我们在谈论一个
few months away at least before this
至少在此之前几个月
code is final but I just think that's
代码是最终的，但我只是认为
really interesting so I we wanted to
真的很有趣，所以我想
sort of show you a demo so let's go
给你看一个演示，让我们开始吧
ahead and bring in spring boot to that
前进并带来春季引导
om7 we use the reactive web support and
om7我们使用反应式网络支持，
I'm gonna bring in a spring cloud
我要带上 Spring 的云
dependency not because I actually need
依赖不是因为我实际上需要
anything from spring cloud but because I
Spring Cloud中的任何东西，但是因为我
want the the maven dependencies and the
想要Maven依赖和
wine and all that stuff and we're still
葡萄酒和所有这些东西，我们仍然
gonna have to do a little bit of setup
要做一些设置
there but that's okay so I'm gonna open
在那里，那没关系，所以我要打开
this up and that should give a spring
这应该给 Spring
Club Finchley m4 m5 alright so we'll
芬奇利俱乐部m4 m5好，我们来
open that up and the first thing that
打开那第一件事
we're gonna need to do before we get too
我们将需要做的之前我们也要做
far down the path is to bring in the
要走的很远是
spring cloud dependencies for Cloud
Cloud的Spring Cloud依赖关系
Foundry right which is which because
铸造权，这是因为
it's not part of the code base yet I
它不是代码库的一部分
sort of we have to I have mean and clean
我们必须要有我的意思和干净
installed it locally but you hopefully
在本地安装，但您希望
won't have this problem by the time
到时候不会有这个问题
you're doing this and so spring cloud
你正在这样做，所以 Spring 的云
cloud foundry dependencies all right -
云代工厂的依赖关系很好-
Toto build snapshot and we'll say that
要构建快照，我们会说
this is a palm and we'll say that the
这是一棵棕榈树，我们会说
scope is import alright so there's the
范围是导入好，所以有
there's that spring cloud 500
那是 Spring 的云500
dependencies and well finally we'll need
依赖，最后我们需要
to bring in spring cloud
带来 Spring 的云
five hundred comments right so comments
五百条评论对，所以评论
this is where the auto-configuration
这是自动配置的地方
lives at the moment like I said that
活在当下，就像我说的那样
might change right this is a separate
可能会改变，这是一个单独的
module that is nothing to do with a
与...无关的模块
service registration and discovery
服务注册和发现
support as well as the other web filters
支持以及其他Web过滤器
that are in the spring cloud platform a
在 Spring Cloud 平台中
sort of module this is a particulate of
某种模块，这是
configuration for the Cloud Foundry
Cloud Foundry的配置
client so maybe a better artifact named
客户，所以也许是一个更好的工件
spring cloud platform to client it'll
Spring 的云平台给客户
it'll change but that we obviously look
它将改变，但我们显然会
at the documentation or they get a
在文档上，否则他们会得到
repository what all is happening okay so
仓库什么都发生了，所以
we've had that all there that gives us
我们拥有的一切都给了我们
an auto configured Cloud Foundry Java
自动配置的Cloud Foundry Java
client and that clad auto configuration
客户端和该自动配置
is there's a lot of moving parts in the
里面有很多活动部件
cloud for new java client
新的Java客户端的云
none of it is particularly hard in fact
实际上，没有一个特别困难
you can you can look at the cloud vendor
你可以看一下云供应商
Java client website and you'll find an
Java客户网站，您会发现
example configuration which shows you
显示您的示例配置
all the moving pieces and but there are
所有的运动件，但是有
a lot of moving pieces so it's just nice
很多移动的东西，所以很好
to have that auto automatically taken
自动选择
care of for us the confident gives us
照顾我们，自信给我们
the ability to write applications as I
像我一样编写应用程序的能力
say that interacts with cloud funding
说与云资金互动
and confident we can do a lot of things
有信心我们可以做很多事情
you can deploy applications you can
您可以部署应用程序
scale them you can create custom routes
缩放它们，您可以创建自定义路线
for them you can you know you can create
为他们，你知道你可以创造吗
backing services you can scale those if
支持服务，如果
you want you can change the plans you
你想改变你的计划
can create service brokers which are
可以创建服务经纪人
basically API is that themselves mediate
基本上API是自己进行中介
access to a backing service something
访问支持服务的东西
like a database or a message queue or
例如数据库或消息队列或
key value store whatever and you can
键值存储什么都可以
install those dynamically and those in
动态安装那些
turn can have dependent sort of backing
转弯可以有依赖的支持
services you can push applications you
您可以推送应用程序的服务
can you know interrogate the API you can
你知道可以查询API吗
deploy custom route services you can do
部署您可以做的自定义路线服务
all sorts of things right you can
各种事情都可以
actually push container images if you
实际推送容器图像，如果您
want you can do all sorts of things here
希望你可以在这里做各种各样的事情
not to mention the security aspects
更何况安全方面
right I mean there's some things that
是的，我的意思是有些事情
are really well done using the client
使用客户端确实做得很好
Java client that there is no equivalent
没有等效的Java客户端
or an analogous
或类似的
sort of command in the CF client itself
CF客户端本身中的某种命令
so in the CF CLI client itself so one
因此在CF CLI客户端本身中
thing that my friend Josh Mackenzie and
我的朋友乔什·麦肯齐（Josh Mackenzie）和
I demonstrated when we did our
我示范了我们什么时候做的
crowdfunding live lessons a
众筹现场课程
for Pearson was using the crowdfunding
因为培生（Pearson）正在使用众筹
Java client to do something across all
Java客户端跨所有功能
the applications in a particular
特定应用
organization or space so suppose we
组织或空间，所以假设我们
wanted to go through all the
想经历所有
applications that were deployed using
使用部署的应用程序
the Java build pack and we knew that the
Java构建包，我们知道
build pack has been updated and there's
构建包已更新，并且
an important important security
重要的重要安全
vulnerability so what I want to do is I
脆弱性，所以我要做的是
want to force cloud sunny to restart the
想要强迫云晴重新启动
apps if they have the java bill pack or
有Java帐单包或
the.net pill pack or whatever if they
the.net药包或其他
use the new bill pec you know if they
使用新的法案佩奇，你知道他们是否
get restarted and they're not pinned to
重新启动并且它们没有固定到
a particular version of the version of
版本的特定版本
the of the build pack then they'll get
的构建包，然后他们会得到
the latest build pack which will have
最新的构建包将具有
the security vulnerability patch so we
安全漏洞补丁，所以我们
want that that's an interesting thing to
希望那是一件有趣的事情
do but there's no like button for that
可以，但是没有类似的按钮
there's no like you know restart just
没有像您知道的那样重启
the job apps for everything in the in
工作应用中的所有内容
there in the organization in space so
在太空中的组织中
you can write that code Fredi easily
您可以轻松编写该代码Fredi
using the Cloud Foundry Java client
使用Cloud Foundry Java客户端
alright so let's see demo and let me
好吧，让我们看一下演示，让我
make this font a little larger my
使这个字体大一点
friends okay I'll say make it 22 very
朋友好吧，我会说使其非常22
good all right so we're gonna have a
好吧，好了，我们要
application runner and the suffocation
应用程序运行程序和窒息
winner is going to need it's going to
获胜者将需要它
you know it's going to be the thing that
你知道那将是
actually holds our business object and
实际上持有我们的业务对象
again there's no reason this has to be
再次没有理由这一定是
an application writer this could be a
一个应用程序编写者，这可能是一个
REST API you can have a rest endpoint a
REST API您可以拥有一个休息端点
spring web flex rest endpoint after all
Spring Web Flex其余端点
this is the spring web flex you know
这是您知道的Spring Web Flex
this is using the reactive web support
这是使用反应式网络支持
not spring MVC but spring web flex and
不是spring MVC，而是spring web flex和
we've talked about that at numerous
我们已经在很多地方谈论过
opportunities in numerous occasions in
在许多场合的机会
previous video so I encourage you to
以前的视频，所以我鼓励您
check those out we could use a rest
检查那些我们可以休息一下
endpoint for example to manipulate the
端点，例如操纵
deployment of this software we could
部署该软件，我们可以
have a spring shell application that's
有一个Spring Shell应用程序
another really compelling option is you
另一个真正引人注目的选择是您
know in a previous video we looked at a
知道在上一个视频中，我们看了
spring shell and we looked at how it can
Spring Shell，我们研究了它如何
be used to to create easy to use shells
用于创建易于使用的外壳
that we can interact with dynamically
我们可以动态互动
there's a ripple you can script it and
你可以编写一个涟漪，然后
so on so imagine having a shell that was
如此想象一下，拥有一个
designed to allow people to deploy your
旨在让人们部署您的
application you could specify custom
您可以指定自定义的应用程序
parameters you could interrogate the
您可以询问的参数
state of the system run health checks do
系统状态运行状况检查
it everyone right you can all do all
每个人都可以做的所有事情
sorts of things and you could also just
各种各样的事情，你也可以
like I say use it sort of in a command
就像我说的在命令中使用它
you know command stop where you just run
你知道命令停止在你刚刚运行的地方
it and it just does something instead of
它，它只是做一些事情而不是
having the ripple so this is just an
有涟漪，所以这只是一个
application runner we're just gonna
应用程序运行器，我们只是
create a logic in there and it's not the
在其中创建逻辑，这不是
only way to go all right all right so
没事的唯一方法就是好
first thing we want to do is want to say
我们要做的第一件事就是说
that we have a jar right we we're gonna
我们有一个罐子，我们要
actually have to deploy a jar somewhere
实际上必须在某个地方部署一个罐子
so let's make sure that we have a jar
因此，请确保我们有一个罐子
let's say that this jar is described by
假设这个罐子是由
a spring framework resource right this
Spring 的框架资源吧
is our jar our binary that we learned
是我们的罐子，我们学到的二进制文件
deploy so let's say jar dot exists the
部署，所以假设jar点存在
jar must exist right we want to fail the
jar必须存在，我们要失败
program if that's not true where does
如果那不是真的，那么在哪里编程
this jar come from well we have to
这个罐子来自好，我们必须
inject it naturally so let's inject it
自然地注入它，所以让我们注入它
as an artifact here let's see it's gonna
作为文物，让我们看看它会
be an artifact you know a jar artifact
做一个神器，你知道罐子神器
there we go that's what we're going to
我们去那就是我们要去的
depend on and I guess that brings us to
依靠，我想这使我们
the next point which is where do we get
接下来的一点是我们从哪里得到
that jar so let's let's run this code
该罐子，让我们运行这段代码
and see what happens obviously it's
看看会发生什么
gonna fail
会失败
right
对
okay good so we have no environment
好的，所以我们没有环境
variable called John artifact so let's
变量称为Johnartifact，让我们
set that up here and we'll set up the
在这里设置，我们将设置
environment variables and we'll create a
环境变量，我们将创建一个
new jar or a new I'm vulnerable you
新罐子或新罐子，我很容易受到伤害
should do this in your conveyor you know
应该在传送带上做到这一点
this could be a command-line argument
这可能是命令行参数
you could use commons ops you know the
您可以使用Commons Ops，您知道
patchy comment ops for example to to
斑驳的评论操作例如
manage environment you know to
管理您知道的环境
parameters you can even use spring
您甚至可以使用spring的参数
property you know configuration property
您知道的属性配置属性
pogos where you actually bind a property
实际绑定属性的pogos
to a beam and then dereference that
到光束，然后取消引用
property in your command line you know
您知道的命令行中的属性
in this application lender you can you
在这个申请贷款人中，你可以吗
could use all sorts of things here you
可以在这里使用各种各样的东西
know if this were a shell this would be
知道这是否是贝壳
something you specify with - - whatever
您指定的内容--随便
jar but in this case that's just hard
罐子，但在这种情况下很难
coded so I'm gonna have to I'm gonna say
编码，所以我要说
that there's gonna be a jar on my
我的身上会有一个罐子
desktop called hideout jar now I don't
现在我不叫桌面的藏身罐
actually have that jar yet so this will
实际上有那个罐子，所以这会
still fail about least we've specified
仍然失败至少我们指定的
in the environment variable which is
在环境变量中
what we want so let's go ahead and
我们想要什么，让我们继续前进，
create that jar for now okay so CD
现在就创建那个罐子吧，所以CD
mcdeere app CD app touch hi dot groovy
mcdeere应用程序CD应用程序touch hi dot groovy
the Emacs aigu be at rest controller
Emacs AIGU静止控制器
readings rests controller alright def hi
读数取决于控制器好吗def hi
path variable string name
路径变量字符串名称
greetings breathing hello alright get
问候呼吸你好好得到
mapping hi name question mark alright
映射嗨名字问号好
good look at that save spring jar
好看看那个保存Spring 罐
hideout groovy I suppose we should run
隐藏的时髦我想我们应该跑
it first let's just do that you know I
首先让我们做一下，你知道我
knew I made a mistake okay let's fix it
知道我犯了一个错误好吧，让我们修复它
here we are
我们来了
what do we do we've got the closing
我们该怎么办
bracket there spring a run and hide out
支架在那里奔跑并躲藏起来
groovy okay looks okay localhost hi
groovy好的看起来不错localhost嗨
world okay that seems you okay
世界还可以，你还可以
spring tips very good good so now spring
Spring 的提示非常好，所以现在 Spring
jar oh we want to create a properly
罐子，我们要正确创建一个
filed application dot properties I'll
我将提交的应用程序点属性
say management dot security Dardenne old
说管理点安全Dardenne老
equals false okay
等于假好吧
spring jar and we want to have the
Spring 罐，我们想要
actuator bits don't we so actually Emacs
执行器位实际上我们不是Emacs
hideout groovy that grab spring boot
抢 spring boot 的藏身之处
starter actuator this will be a cloud
起动器执行器这将是云
friendly application after all so spring
毕竟如此 Spring
jar hideout jar Java - John Hyde up jar
罐子藏身罐Java-John Hyde罐子
let's see if that works good that seemed
让我们看看看起来是否很好
ok e and V alright good so now copy
好的e和V好吧，所以现在复制
hideout jar to the desktop and that
隐藏罐子到桌面，那
should match what our environment
应该符合我们的环境
vailable is expecting let's try this
期待我们尝试一下
[Music]
[音乐]
nor must exist it doesn't not exist
也必须存在它不存在
let's see home Jhelum desktop hi there
让我们看看那里的Jhelum桌面吧
it is home Jang just a pie-chart effect
这是张家的家，只是一个饼图效果
oh it needs to be resolved using a file
哦，需要使用文件来解决
prefix there okay why is let's restart
前缀那里好吧，为什么让我们重新启动
IntelliJ here it's giving me no end of
IntelliJ在这里给我无限的机会
trouble see demo we want idea on that
麻烦看演示我们想要的想法
XML alright
好的XML
all right so we have our application
好的，所以我们有我们的应用程序
let's see if we can run this again do we
让我们看看是否可以再次运行它
still have our environment variable that
仍然有我们的环境变量
is the question of course not so we
当然不是问题了，所以我们
called this the jar artifact and it will
称之为罐子神器，它将
be equal to home jail own desktop
等于家庭监狱自己的桌面
hideout jar all right and
藏身罐好吧，
run that again
再次运行
okay
好的
run is shift f10 so shift function f2
运行是移位f10，所以移位函数f2
alright okay it looks like it's happy so
好吧，看起来很高兴，所以
now what do we want to we want to deploy
现在我们要部署什么
our application well actually before we
我们的应用程序实际上在我们之前
deploy our application we need to apply
部署我们的应用程序，我们需要申请
the service so to do all right number
服务好吧号
one well number one is deploy the P my
一口井是部署P my
sequel backing service right so what do
续集支持服务正确怎么办
I mean by this well if you've ever used
我的意思是，如果您曾经使用过
cloud foreigner you know that it has a
云外国人，你知道它有一个
great catalog so CF catalog or
很棒的目录，所以CF目录或
marketplace rather it has a service
市场而不是有服务
marketplace and this marketplace changes
市场和这个市场的变化
from one cotton installation to another
从一个棉花安装到另一个
right now we're using pivotal Web
现在我们正在使用关键网络
Services is the hosted multi tenant sort
服务是托管的多租户排序
of installation of crowdfunding that
安装众筹的过程
pivotal itself maintains on public cloud
关键本身维持在公共云上
infrastructure and so we we use for our
基础设施，因此我们将其用于
backing services we use different cloud
支持服务，我们使用不同的云
providers you know software is the
您知道软件的提供商
service providers and these are all very
服务提供商，这些都非常
good very very useful if you're running
很好，非常有用，如果您正在跑步
on premise you might have services that
在前提条件下，您可能会提供
your organization feels need to be there
您的组织感觉需要在那里
so you've deployed them yourself you
所以你自己部署了它们
might have the one to come with pivotal
可能会有一个关键的
Cloud Foundry which a lot of times are
很多时候的Cloud Foundry
different than the ones you'll see
与您看到的不同
hosted here and if you're using a public
托管在这里，如果您使用公共场所
cloud like Google or Microsoft well they
像Google或Microsoft这样的云
have and maintain their own service
有并保持自己的服务
brokers for things that are unique and
经纪人的独特和
value-adding in those different
这些不同的增值
environments so you can use a you know a
环境，以便您可以使用
big table for example and Google in
例如大桌子和谷歌在
Google Cloud for running pivotal cloud
Google Cloud用于运行关键云
funding on top of Google cloud you'll
在Google云端之上提供资金
see you know a service broker that
看到你认识一个服务经纪人
allows you to to talk to those things so
可以让您与这些话题交谈
here we've got a number of different
在这里，我们有很多不同的
services here I well I want to use P my
我这里的服务我想用P我的
sequel for example this is a good one
例如续集，这是一个很好的
when you look at the catalog you see
当您查看目录时，您会看到
that the one that has no asterisk this
没有星号的那个
is the this is a single entry right this
这是一个条目吗
is the name of the service provider on
是上的服务提供商的名称
the Left the different plans here
左这里的不同计划
separated by commas the one that has no
用逗号分隔没有
asterisk is free so all these service
星号是免费的，因此所有这些服务
brokers all these service providers have
所有这些服务提供商的经纪人
to have a free tier so you can try
拥有免费套餐，因此您可以尝试
something out a lot of them are all free
有些东西都是免费的
you know they just want you to to use it
你知道他们只是想让你使用它
right but you can see that there's
是的，但是你可以看到
asterisks by the ones that are not free
不自由的星号
so you'll talk to you to make sure you
所以你会跟你说话以确保你
kind of kind of
有点像
consultant the service broker its
咨询服务经纪人
service provider to figure out costs in
服务提供商找出成本
time but a lot of them are free under
时间，但其中许多是免费的
like I said almost all of them aside for
就像我说的，几乎所有人都在旁边
I know as far as I know they should all
据我所知，他们都应该
be free and they sent one tier alright
自由了，他们派了一层
so we want to use PMI sequel because why
所以我们要使用PMI续集，因为
not it's a simple my sequel database our
不是一个简单的续集数据库
application doesn't use my sequel but
应用程序不使用我的续集，但
this is neither here nor there what we
这既不是这里也不是我们
want to do is one let's suppose our
我们想做的是一个
little our little jar our hideout jar
小我们的小罐子我们的藏身罐
required my sequel right now we can't
现在需要我的续集，我们不能
start it up without having my sequel
没有我的续集就开始
instance bound to the application if we
实例绑定到应用程序，如果我们
were to bind a my sequence since the
自从
application what confident will do is it
应用程序充满信心的是
will inject an environment variable into
将环境变量注入
the running process that contains your
包含您的运行过程
your Java code in this case our goofy
在这种情况下，您的Java代码就显得愚蠢
Springwood app and that invited rebel
Springwood应用程序和邀请叛逆者
contains the credentials required to
包含所需的凭据
talk to that my sequence if the my
与我的顺序交谈，如果我的
sequence should ever fail or whatever
顺序应该永远失败
your platform your service provider will
您的平台，您的服务提供商将
provide different environment variables
提供不同的环境变量
that will point you to a different
那会把你指向不同的
instance where the same data hopefully
希望有相同数据的实例
is available it's up to the cloud
是否可用取决于云
provider to maintain things like backups
提供者维护诸如备份之类的东西
and so on but the point is our code
依此类推，但关键是我们的代码
doesn't need to change we just hydrate
不需要改变，我们只需补水
those credentials from the environment
这些来自环境的凭证
variable that's one of the tents of a 12
变量是12的帐篷之一
fact trap is that it's stateless and we
事实陷阱是它是无状态的，我们
can point it to different services from
可以将其指向不同的服务
in development in QA and staging
在质量保证和阶段开发中
production and in multiple environments
生产和多种环境
in production right if we move it from
如果我们从
one container to another one data
一个容器到另一个数据
centers in another should just be a
在另一个中心应该只是一个
matter of changing out the environment
改变环境的问题
variable and that's what currently does
变量，这就是当前的功能
for you right we maintain that that
为了您，我们坚持认为
management that that bookkeeping we make
我们做的簿记管理
sure that those environment rebels point
确保那些环境造反者指出
to things that you can actually use and
可以实际使用的东西
that have been provisioned for you and
为您准备的
whose credentials have been made
已取得其凭证
exclusive explicitly and exclusively for
专门针对
your application so I want to create
您的应用程序，所以我想创建
those those that that backing service
那些支持服务的人
first of all so let's do that let's say
首先，让我们这样做
you want to create a a service so I'm
您想创建一个服务，所以我
gonna say we want to create a service if
要说我们想创建一个服务，如果
misting if it's if it's there if it's
如果它在那儿就在雾中
not there right so if great service
没有那里，所以如果优质的服务
instance if missing and what I'm going
实例，如果丢失，我要去
to do when I use a a key my sequel I
当我用我的续集我要做
guess we said soapy
猜猜我们说肥皂
- my sequel and we want to we want to
-我的续集，我们想要我们想要
have a particular name so let's call it
有一个特殊的名字，所以我们称它为
you know bring tips my sequel and we
你知道带提示我的续集，我们
want the what I want well I think we
想要我想要的东西，我想我们
should get the free one right and we'll
应该获得免费的权利，我们将
talk about how we specify that in a
谈论我们如何在
second but let's say that we have this
第二个，但说我们有这个
method that takes two strings
需要两个字符串的方法
okay great service if missing all right
好的，服务很好，如果没事的话
so string is going to be the service
所以字符串将成为服务
name and then the instance name the one
名称，然后实例名称之一
that we want the logical name you want
我们想要您想要的逻辑名称
to give it so that we can refer to it
给它，以便我们可以参考它
later on alright so we're gonna we're
以后好吧，我们要去
going to create a service instance if
如果要创建服务实例
it's missing and we have to do some
它丢失了，我们必须做一些
pretty you know we have to interrogate
漂亮，你知道我们必须审问
the state of the system to make that
使该系统状态
work so let's let's see how we do this
工作，让我们看看我们如何做到这一点
first of all I want to want to look at
首先，我想看看
the the API when you need to work with
需要使用API​​时
the API so we can inject that API here
API，因此我们可以在此处注入该API
using the the aforementioned auto
使用上述自动
configured Cloud Foundry Java client so
配置了Cloud Foundry Java客户端，因此
I'm going to use the Cloud Foundry
我将使用Cloud Foundry
operations here and I call this
这里的操作，我称之为
operations will inject that into the
操作会将其注入
constructor of the application very good
应用程序的构造函数非常好
and now I can put that upstairs there we
现在我可以把它放在楼上
go now we are going to say that
现在去，我们要说
we want to first figure out if if the
我们要首先弄清楚是否
service already exists right so we say
服务已经存在，所以我们说
this that operation has dot services and
该操作具有点服务，
I guess we can list the instances and
我想我们可以列出实例和
then we going to filter right we're
然后我们要过滤对
going to filter the instances so I'm
要过滤实例，所以我
going to say filter si and we're going
要说过滤器si，我们要
to say si don't get named so aside I get
说我没有名字所以我不知道
name dot equals ignore case instance
名称点等于忽略大小写实例
name or sorry yeah instance name right
名称或对不起，实例名称正确
so there's that now this will give us
所以现在这将给我们
back a publisher that will have you know
向发布商询问您的情况
one Dominion if we had just done list it
如果我们刚刚完成列出一个自治领
would have given us all of the services
会给我们所有的服务
but here we're filtering down to just
但是在这里，我们只过滤到
the one that we want you notice how easy
我们希望您注意到的那一件事很容易
that was it you know kind of kind of
那就是你知道的那种
rolls right off the tongue right I said
我说过的话从舌头上滚下来
this dot operations I said I want to
这个点操作我说我想
work with services then I want to
使用服务，然后我想
specifically look at all the listings of
具体看一下所有的清单
them and then I want to filter that
他们，然后我想过滤
right if I had done this that operations
对，如果我这样做了
dot applications of a
点应用
support there for working with
支持在那里与
applications for managing organizations
管理组织的申请
from managing build packs the advanced
从管理构建包进阶
thing itself gives us sh code you know
事情本身给了我们您知道的sh代码
that's not too interesting Network
这不太有趣
policies you know dynamic network
您知道动态网络的策略
policies routes service administration
政策路由服务管理
space administration spaces themselves
空间管理空间本身
stacks like are you running
像你在跑的堆栈
are you deploying your apps to Linux you
您是否正在将应用程序部署到Linux？
know cut under Linux stems stem cells
知道在Linux干细胞下切割
are using Windows virtual machines
正在使用Windows虚拟机
I started Windows containers basically
我基本上是启动Windows容器的
in Windows Windows Server 2016 you know
在Windows Windows Server 2016中，您知道
all this stuff is described here and
所有这些东西都在这里描述和
modeled by this API but you had the
以此API为模型，但您有
scenes it's talking to a REST API
与REST API对话的场景
alright so it's talking to a REST API
好了，所以它正在与REST API通讯
but we don't have to worry about that we
但我们不必担心我们
have it's nice type safe client that
有一个很好的类型安全客户端
knows about all this stuff for us so
为我们知道所有这些东西
there's our publisher that'll tell us if
有我们的出版商会告诉我们
something is a if something exists right
如果某物存在正确的话
so existing now what we want to do is we
所以现在我们要做的是
want to we want to create the service
想要我们想要创建服务
right first one our creative service but
首先是我们的创意服务，但
only if there are no existing ones so
只有在没有现存的情况下
we're gonna say that we want to do
我们会说我们想做
existing thought switch if empty right
现有的思想开关（如果为空）
so if this publisher if this publisher
所以如果这个发布者
comes back and it has no value remember
回来，它没有价值，记得
this is a reactive streams publisher
这是反应式流发布者
it's a it's a object that will notify us
这是一个会通知我们的对象
whenever there's a new record it'll
每当有新记录时
notify us that that notification is
通知我们该通知是
called and you know it's going to emit
打电话，你知道它会发出
an object right well in this case it may
在这种情况下正确的对象可能
not omit anything if it emits nothing
如果不发出任何东西就不要遗漏
then it's empty and we want to have to
那么它是空的，我们想要
we have to sort of switch streams
我们必须要分类切换流
basically right we can't continue
基本上正确，我们无法继续
processing we can't chain anything after
处理后，我们不能链接任何东西
that because there's no there's nothing
那是因为没有没有
that's gonna happen so we need to switch
那将会发生，所以我们需要切换
and use a different publisher instead to
并改用其他发布商
handle this request so that's what we're
处理这个要求，这就是我们
gonna do so what we're going to do is
要做的是我们要做的是
switch to a crate right let's switch to
切换到板条箱右侧，让我们切换到
a crate there and then we'll just return
一个板条箱在那里，然后我们将返回
a single or empty and this will be a you
一个或一个空的，这将是一个你
know result all right
知道结果没事
so mono of service instance summary so
这样的服务实例摘要如此
we need to have a crate call in there
我们需要在这里打电话
somewhere and that crate is going to say
一个地方，那个箱子会说
this operations dot services dot list
此操作点服务点列表
service offerings and what we want to do
服务产品以及我们要做什么
is now we're looking at the catalogue
现在我们在看目录
right before we were looking at all the
就在我们查看所有
provisioned services that we already
提供我们已经提供的服务
have in our account you know did I
在我们的帐户中，您知道我吗
already create a instance of this
已经创建了一个实例
service and but you know and is it
服务，但是你知道并且是
already given a logical name if so it
如果已经给出了逻辑名
would be called instance name now I'm
我现在将被称为实例名称
looking at the catalog in order to do
查看目录以做
that I need to send a command and this
我需要发送命令，这
is a where they the the crowdfunder Java
是他们众筹Java的地方
plan is kind of interesting there's
计划很有意思
these heavy use of builders and take it
这些大量使用建设者并接受它
take it or leave it but it uh it is what
接受或离开它，但是它是什么
we have to use here and you know it's
我们必须在这里使用，你知道这是
was such a big API that's so flexible I
这么大的API太灵活了
think this actually gives you a you know
认为这实际上给了你一个你知道的
it's you can do everything you need to
这是您可以做的所有事情
do it's my point is there's no there's
这是我的观点，没有那里
nothing that's being hidden from you so
没有什么对你隐藏
that's kind of that's kind of nice so
那样很好，所以
I'm gonna say look at the catalog and
我要说看目录
then filter the results that come back
然后过滤返回的结果
and remember I'm giving a service
记得我在提供服务
offering so I'm gonna predict I want a
提供，所以我要预测我想要一个
filter to serve offerings and I would
筛选以提供产品，我会
say if the label equals the service that
说标签是否等于服务
we want to look at service name then I
我们想看看服务名称，然后我
want to take that resulting you know
想要得到的结果你知道
right now we've got a publisher if you
现在我们有一家出版商，如果您
looked at this this is actually a
看着这实际上是一个
publisher of data right this is a crate
数据发布者，这是一箱
publisher so it's a publisher of service
发布者，因此它是服务的发布者
offerings right now and we want to
现在提供产品，我们希望
actually filter that and turn that into
实际过滤并将其转化为
something else so this is where we
其他的东西，所以这是我们
called flatmap so I'm gonna take the
叫做flatmap，所以我要
Esso here and we'll say in our flat map
埃索在这里，我们将在平面图中说
that we're gonna create a we're gonna
我们要创造一个我们要
get the service plant right so this
确定服务工厂的正确性
service offering has service plans which
服务提供中有哪些服务计划
is the collection of service plants so
是服务工厂的集合，所以
we're gonna get the service plans assign
我们将分配服务计划
that to a variable here
到这里的变量
plans and in the plans we're going to
计划以及在计划中
visit the plans and see if any of them
参观计划，看看是否有任何计划
are free right so this is where we want
是自由的权利，所以这是我们想要的
to figure out how it's free so I'm gonna
弄清楚它是免费的，所以我要
say plans dream dot filter and I'm gonna
说计划梦点过滤器，我要
need a predicate which says basically
需要一个谓词，基本上
service plan is free right now this
服务计划现在免费
should be pluggable I say this would be
应该是可插入的，我说这将是
something that would be nice to have
有些东西会很高兴
pluggable so here we're going to say
可插拔的，所以在这里我们要说
predicate service plan pregnant kit
谓词服务计划怀孕工具包
right sort of time predicate here we'll
正确的时间谓词在这里，我们将
say service plan predicate and we want
说服务计划谓词，我们想要
to find the first one that comes back
找到第一个回来的
any of them maybe there's only gonna be
他们中的任何一个也许只有
one or it's not you know we didn't with
一个或不是你知道我们没有
it will work but we want Indian really
它会工作，但我们真的想要印度人
or first one it doesn't matter I suppose
还是第一个我想都没关系
and if one comes back great that'll give
如果一个人回来很棒，那将会给
us a stream containing their first
我们包含他们的第一个流
record right actually in this case it'll
在这种情况下实际上记录正确
give us an optional right so I don't
给我们一个可选的权利，所以我不
want the optional I need to actually get
想要我实际需要的可选件
the value that's in there or we need to
那里的价值，否则我们需要
throw an exception something is very
抛出异常是非常非常的
wrong so or else throw you know new
错了，不然会让你知道新的
runtime exception so runtime exception
运行时异常，所以运行时异常
couldn't find a service couldn't find a
找不到服务找不到服务
service called service name right so
服务称为服务名称正确
that's that's the okay you want to sign
那就是你要签署的没关系
up to a variable there a service plan so
直到变量存在服务计划，所以
there's a free service plan free service
有免费服务计划免费服务
instance that we want so I'll say free
我们想要的实例，所以我会说免费
and what I want to do is I want to use
我想做的就是使用
that to create a service instance right
创建服务实例的权利
so we're going to create a service
所以我们要创建一个服务
instance we're going to say I'm this dot
实例，我们要说我是这个点
recite operations thought services dot
背诵操作思想服务点
create instance and want to pass in a
创建实例并想要传递一个
create service instance request so
创建服务实例请求，以便
create service instance
创建服务实例
request dot builder dot and then we're
请求点构建器点，然后我们
going to pass in the plan name and the
将传递计划名称和
plan name of course is the free plan
套餐名称当然是免费套餐
name so there is our name up there and
名字，所以我们的名字在那里
we're going to pass in the service name
我们将传递服务名称
and that should be the service name up
那应该是服务名称
there and we're going to pass in the
在那里，我们将通过
service instance name and that's gonna
服务实例名称，然后
be the instance name and I think that'll
是实例名称，我认为
be everything we need so let's hit build
成为我们需要的一切，让我们开始建设
now this will give us a request that we
现在这将给我们一个要求
can pass in there so it's a paid service
可以通过那里，所以这是一项付费服务
instance request great press it there
实例请求伟大按那里
alright so we've got now a a bit of code
好了，所以我们现在有了一些代码
here we're creating a we're going to
在这里，我们要创建一个
create the service instance using the
使用创建服务实例
service you know services sub grouping
您知道的服务服务子分组
of functionality in the operations and
操作中的功能和
the - under operations on ap I know by
-我知道的关于ap的操作
the way going back to that the platform
回到平台的方式
the operations API is a kind of
操作API是一种
high-level thing it's a it's a a it you
高级的东西，这是一个，你
know it has all the functionality
知道它具有所有功能
high-level functionality that you'd
您想要的高级功能
expect if you were using the C f/c Li
期待您使用的是C f / c Li
and that functionality is nicely grouped
而且该功能很好地分组了
into these sort of sub api's and they in
进入这类子api，
turn have to compose lower level
轮到不得不组成较低的水平
primitives there's actually something
原始物实际上有一些东西
called a Cloud Foundry client and the
称为Cloud Foundry客户端，
client funded client is very low level
客户资助的客户水平很低
it's it provides more control so if you
它提供了更多控制权，因此，如果您
can't find what you need in the in the
在中找不到您需要的东西
cloud for the operations you might check
云为您可能检查的操作
the client but the client doesn't always
客户，但客户并不总是
have what you want for example the work
有你想要的东西，例如工作
of actually pushing an application to
实际将应用程序推送到
the platform which is to say deploying
平台即部署
the application it's actually composed
实际组成的应用程序
itself of many other smaller things and
本身还有许多其他较小的事物，
all that all those individual things are
所有那些个别的东西都是
what you would find here in the client
您将在客户端找到的内容
the portion operation itself though is
部分操作本身是
is actually here the operations API so
实际上是操作API，因此
you know a lot of things are happening
你知道很多事情正在发生
when you do a push it's getting services
当您进行推送时，它将获得服务
it's putting route it's pushing an
它正在推路线，正在推
application it's doing all sorts of
应用程序正在做各种各样的事情
stuff that you can't you can take for
你不能拿的东西
granted if you want to but if you want
如果您愿意的话可以授予
to pick apart that particular
分开那个细节
you can do so by digging into the client
您可以通过深入研究客户端来做到这一点
all right so we now we have them we we
好的，所以我们现在有他们，我们
do need to provide that extra operator
确实需要提供额外的运算符
there so it's a service plan is free
在那里，这是一项服务计划是免费的
great that's our our provided value
太好了，这就是我们提供的价值
there all right so now we've got now
那里好吧，现在我们有了
we're saying we're saying that we want
我们是说我们要
to create a service and then when we
创建服务，然后当我们
turn this now the return value here
现在将其设为此处的返回值
isn't super useful right it's a what do
不是超级有用的权利，这是做什么的
we get if we if we assign this it's a
我们得到如果我们分配给它，这是一个
void right that's not exactly what we
无效的权利不完全是我们
want so what I want to do is I want to
想要所以我想做的是
say then I want to find the existing
说然后我想找到现有的
service instance now I want to confirm
现在我要确认服务实例
that everything has been written just by
一切都只是由
reading the data again so I'll then say
再次读取数据，所以我会说
then many existing and of course that
那么很多现有的，当然
flips this up into a service instance
将其翻转为服务实例
summary as well so create so we're gonna
总结，所以创建，所以我们要
what we're going to do is we're going to
我们要做的是
create the we're going to go through and
创建我们将要经历的
create it and then return it by
创建它，然后将其返回
searching for it you know the rights
搜索它，您知道权利
linking to that we're going to write I'm
链接到我们要写的是
gonna create a new service and they're
要创建一个新服务，他们
going to look up that service and return
将查找该服务并返回
a publisher that contains that service
包含该服务的发布者
and the actual logic is as follows we're
实际的逻辑如下
gonna say look for it you know if it's
会说寻找它，你知道是否
there created and then whatever you do
在那里创建，然后无论您做什么
take the flux that comes back right now
吸收现在返回的流量
you would have a flux right this is the
你会有助焊剂的权利，这是
result of this is actually a flux well
结果实际上是通量良好
we know that it's only gonna be one
我们知道那只会是一个
object so we just say take it and then
对象，所以我们只说接受它，然后
turn it into a mono and in the reactive
把它变成单声道
world in the reactor world a mono is a
单核反应堆是一个世界
publisher that produces zero or one
产生零或一的发布者
values and flux is a publisher that
价值观和变化是出版商
produces 0 to n values where and it
在其中产生0到n值
could be infinite right so we're we're
可能是无限的权利，所以我们
saying that we wanted to return we want
说我们想返回我们想要
to say when I look for the existing
说当我寻找现有的
record if there is no existing record
如果没有现有记录，则记录
then use this publisher which will
然后使用该发布者
create a new one and of course it will
创建一个新的，当然它将
conclude itself by returning you know if
通过返回您知道自己是否结束
they exist it'll look for the existing
他们存在，它将寻找现有的
one and then we turn the whole thing
一个，然后我们把整个事情
into a result we return it there
结果我们将其返回
so let's return that all like so and
所以让我们返回所有这样的
this implies that we need a publisher
这意味着我们需要一个发布者
that takes that return to service
才能恢复服务
instance summary so this is a mono of
实例摘要，所以这是
service instance summary alright there's
服务实例摘要还可以
our create service instance if missing
如果缺少我们的创建服务实例
now this is all one big publisher write
现在这就是一个大出版商写的
this this actually is all these
这实际上就是所有这些
different things all these different
所有这些不同的东西
little flows and branches and all that
小流量和分支等等
all combined into one big publisher that
全部合并成一个大发行商
has multiple steps or stages that can be
有多个步骤或阶段可以
a pipeline right the reactor engine can
反应堆发动机可以通过的管道
pipeline that for us it can it can
对我们来说可以的管道
manage that for us now of course here
现在当然在这里为我们管理
you know create service here we have a
你知道在这里创建服务，我们有一个
we have a publisher nothing is gonna
我们有一个出版商，什么都没有
happen yet right nothing is happening
发生了，没事了
yet because we actually need to visit
但是因为我们实际上需要参观
the data that comes back and we need
返回的数据，我们需要
that you know the result of that is a is
您知道那是一个结果是
that we actually have to to subscribe to
我们实际上必须订阅
it again in the reactive world a
在反应世界中又一次
publisher doesn't activate nothing
发布者什么都不激活
happens if I were to run this code
如果我运行这段代码会发生
nothing that we just wrote would
我们刚才写的没有
activate nothing would actually execute
激活什么都不会实际执行
until somebody calls subscribe on the
直到有人打电话订阅
publisher so we're gonna have one
发布者，所以我们要一个
publisher so we're just gonna say
发布者，所以我们只想说
subscribe here and we're gonna assume
在这里订阅，我们将假设
that the last thing that's emitted from
从那发出的最后一件事
the publisher is going to be just you
发布者将是你
know a confirmation that we're done
知道我们已经完成的确认
right so we're gonna say X love that
对，所以我们要说X爱那个
info and we need a log care so let's get
信息，我们需要日志护理，让我们开始吧
a log log equals log factory doctor get
日志日志等于日志工厂医生获取的日志
along good class alright we're going to
一路走好，我们要
say info your application has been
说出您的申请信息
deployed and bound to the service ok we
部署并绑定到服务好吧，我们
need this single quotes it took you know
需要这个单引号，你知道
seconds to deploy all right
数秒即可部署
now we need to provide some string
现在我们需要提供一些字符串
format parameters there and the in this
在那里格式化参数
case it's it's useful to extract this
情况下，提取这个很有用
out so this is the service name alright
出来，所以这是服务名称
and there's the service instance name
还有服务实例名称
and we'll pass this in we're going to
我们将通过这个，
say your application is called what I'm
说你的申请叫我
going to call this well we need to give
要称呼这个好，我们需要给
it a name right so we know that wouldn't
它的名字正确，所以我们知道不会
be deploying an application here soon so
即将在这里部署应用程序
let's call this string app name equals
我们将此字符串称为应用程序名称等于
st app alright for spring tips app so
st app春季提示应用程序还不错
your application okay has been deployed
您的应用程序已经部署好了
and bound to the service called instance
并绑定到称为实例的服务
name which we're going to rename to be
我们将重命名为的名称
service instance name and we need to
服务实例名称，我们需要
provide a duration all right so let's
提供一个持续时间，所以让我们
actually start the clock ticking right
实际上开始计时正确
before long start equal system dot
早于等于系统点
current time milliseconds and that'll be
当前时间毫秒，这将是
system dot current time the late - start
系统点当前时间晚启动
so we'll see the duration delta here ok
所以我们会在这里看到持续时间增量
so what does that give us that gives us
那给我们带来了什么呢？
an error we need to compile this for it
一个错误，我们需要为此编译
to run string that format good there we
运行格式良好的字符串
are ok so there's our first publisher
好的，所以我们有第一个出版商
we're gonna we're gonna actually you
我们要我们实际上是你
know that'll do it doesn't do much right
知道这样做会做的不好
what its gonna do is it's gonna create
它要做的是创造
the service if it doesn't exist so let's
服务，如果它不存在，那么让我们
go see if I've already got the service
去看看我是否已经得到服务
ok CF s alright so I'm going to delete
好的CF没问题，所以我要删除
this CF t minus F C and jameise equal
这个CF t减去FC和jameise相等
whatever acts I don't need to delete
我不需要删除的任何行为
anything
任何东西
I can't though do I want that one
我虽然不能想要那个
no it's fine
不，还好
CFS we've got two services CF D - f CN j
CFS我们有两项服务CF D-f CN j
HD a good let's get rid of that and then
高清是一个好习惯，让我们摆脱它，然后
we're going to delete the CN j my sequel
我们将删除CN j我的续集
those are the two apps i need the card
那是我需要卡的两个应用
DV for later for other reasons but point
DV由于其他原因稍后会指出
is right now I've only got one service
现在我只有一项服务
and I have no apps okay so now let's run
我还没有任何应用程序，所以现在让我们运行
this code let's see what happened so
这段代码让我们看看发生了什么
we'll say I want it to run
我们会说我要它运行
okay so again it's a web application one
好的，再次是一个Web应用程序
thing that's interesting is it you have
有趣的是你有
to understand this pipeline could
了解这个管道可以
process it could run asynchronously
进程可以异步运行
right so this is this command line
对，所以这是此命令行
Runner well it may well finish long
跑步者，它可能会长久完成
before this publisher is done working
在此发布者完成工作之前
which is why if you don't have something
这就是为什么如果你没有东西
that like the web flex API or a spring
就像Web Flex API或spring
MVC keeping a socket opening and thus
MVC保持插座打开，因此
keeping the process running you may
保持流程运行，您可能会
think that this isn't working it's
认为这是行不通的
asynchronous right this there's no
异步对，这没有
there's no reason that this publisher
没有理由这个发布者
has to execute its different stages on
必须执行其不同阶段
the main thread it could it could and
它可以做的主线程
often will execute on other fit and you
通常会以其他方式执行，而您
can control that of course by saying I
可以说我当然可以控制
want to subscribe on to a particular
想订阅一个特定的
scheduler so scheduler or dot you know
调度程序，所以您知道调度程序或点
elastic or here's a elastic scheduler
弹性的或弹性调度程序
and with them time to live and all that
和他们在一起生活的时间
stuff or you can do all sorts of stuff
东西，或者你可以做各种各样的事情
here to control scheduling but keep that
在这里控制计划，但要保持
in mind try this the beginning of this
记住尝试这个开始
the the beginning here is not you know
开始不是在这里
the end it is not captured here it's
最终在这里没有被捕获
captured in the last stage in the
在最后阶段捕获
pipeline right okay so that's that's
管道正确，就是这样
certainly interesting and of itself
本身很有趣
let's see if that worked CF s good so
让我们来看看CF是否有效
there's spring tips my sequel that
有 Spring 的提示，我的续集是
created what happens if we run the code
创建了如果我们运行代码会发生什么
again right we know that it is supposed
再次正确，我们知道这应该
to do the right thing if it's already
做正确的事，如果已经
there you should leave it alone if it's
在那里，如果它是
not there we should get the results so
不在那里，我们应该得到结果，所以
there's that okay so nothing has changed
没关系，所以什么都没有改变
and it's fine
很好
okay so now we want to deploy the
好吧，现在我们要部署
application right I want to deploy the
我要部署的应用程序权限
application and then we want to deploy
应用程序，然后我们要部署
and then bind it right so that's
然后将其正确绑定，这样
actually deploy the application now so
现在实际部署应用程序
we've got a publisher that creates the
我们有一家发布商
service instance if it's missing now I
服务实例，如果现在不见了
want to deploy the application so I'm
想部署应用程序，所以我
going to say push application and the
会说推送应用程序和
application will take the app name and
应用程序将使用应用程序名称和
how many replicas do we want I guess
我想我们要多少个副本
want to for now why not and we'll pass
现在想要为什么不这样做，我们会通过
in the jar and do we want to start the
在罐子里，我们要开始
application let's say we don't want to
假设我们不想
start it right we're going to push but
正确开始，我们将继续努力，但是
we don't want to start its own
我们不想开始自己的
crowdfunding if you deploy an
众筹（如果您部署了
application but you need things like the
应用程序，但您需要诸如
backing service you want to bind it
您想要绑定它的支持服务
before you start the application
在启动应用程序之前
otherwise the application will start up
否则应用程序将启动
and look for
并寻找
or message queue or whatever it's gonna
或消息队列或其他任何内容
fail so there's no point in starting up
失败，所以启动毫无意义
we want to deploy the application though
我们虽然想部署应用程序
so that it has a logical name and so
因此它有一个逻辑名称
that we can refer to it and manipulate
我们可以参考它并进行操作
it but we don't want to start it so
它，但我们不想启动它
let's create that method called push ok
让我们创建一个称为push ok的方法
replicas jar start you know start right
复制副本jar开始，您知道开始正确了
so we want to not start it I guess is
所以我们不想开始
the right way to say it so we don't want
说正确的方式，所以我们不想
to start it that's true okay so let's go
开始它是真的，所以让我们开始吧
back to this and in the push we're going
回到这一点，在推动中，我们要
to we're gonna actually push the
到我们实际上要推动
application jar itself so I'm going to
应用程序jar本身，所以我要
say path path equals this is the Java
说路径路径等于这是Java
and IO file library of course I'm going
和IO文件库，我当然要去
to say jar get file got to path right
说jar获取文件到达正确的路径
good
好
and we'll add on an exception here throw
我们将在这里添加一个例外
this exception good and then we want to
这个例外很好，然后我们想
say we turn off plus the operations dot
说我们关闭加上操作点
applications dot push and going to push
应用程序点推送和即将推送
the application to the platform and this
平台上的应用程序
application
应用
you know is going to have its gonna use
你知道会用到的
the the the path that we've just created
我们刚刚创建的路径
so PTH there we're gonna say no start no
所以PTH那里我们要说不开始不
start we're going to give it a a
开始，我们要给它一个
instance count so instances replicas
实例计数，因此实例副本
rather we're going to tell it that we
而是我们要告诉我们
wanted to have a particular name so
想要有一个特定的名字，所以
we'll give it the app name there and I
我们将在其中为其指定应用名称
think that'll be enough thinking about
认为这足以考虑
it here okay that's enough so then what
在这里，就足够了，那又怎样
do we want to do we wanted to confirm
我们想做我们想确认吗
that we got the data that we want to
我们得到了想要的数据
confirm that the application is done so
确认申请已完成
then we'll say operations dot
那我们说点运算
applications dot get get an application
应用程序点获取获取应用程序
request that builder that whatever dot
要求那个建造者那个点
name app name all right so what does
为应用命名，可以吗？
that give us if we assign this to
如果我们将其分配给
results app details mano all right
结果应用程序详细信息mano好的
so there's our application details so
所以这里有我们的申请细节
when we turn that that's actually going
当我们转向那实际上
to return or when we turn here
返回或当我们转过这里
all right and looks like we have
好吧，看起来我们有
everything we need there so if we think
我们在那里需要的一切，如果我们认为
about what we've just done we want to
关于我们刚刚想做的事情
compose that right again this is all big
再次撰写，这是很大的
one big pup publishing a pipeline so we
一个大的小狗发布管道，所以我们
can actually say first create the
可以说先创建
service if it's missing and then do the
服务，如果它丢失，然后执行
following
以下
right pause this is publishing pipeline
右暂停，这是发布管道
and then want to subscribe to that right
然后想订阅该权利
and so see how clean that is for
所以看看那有多干净
actually deploying we're saying first
实际部署我们首先要说的是
create the service instance if it's
创建服务实例（如果有）
missing then after this is done run this
缺少然后完成此操作
and then as this is producing values
然后，因为这正在产生价值
subscribe alright now remember we told
现在订阅好，记得我们告诉过
it to not start it so we actually need
它不会启动它，所以我们实际上需要
to restart it now right we need to start
现在重新启动它，我们需要开始
the application but we actually also
应用程序，但实际上
need to bind the service so we push the
需要绑定服务，所以我们推
application but there is at the moment
应用程序，但目前有
no indication that this application
没有迹象表明该应用程序
should be bound to the service so we
应该绑定到服务，所以我们
need to say then then bind application
需要说然后绑定应用程序
to service instance and the application
服务实例和应用程序
name should be passed in first and then
应先输入名称，然后再输入
the service name a second alright so
服务名称第二个好吧
let's go here create that method alright
让我们在这里创建该方法好吧
and here we're going to use the
在这里，我们将使用
operations thing again I'm going to say
再说一次操作
return this dot operations dot what I
返回这个点操作点我
want I guess we want to services that
我想我们想为您服务
bind find service instance request on
在以下位置绑定查找服务实例请求
builder and here we're going to use the
生成器，在这里我们将使用
service instance name service instance
服务实例名称服务实例
name an application name app name and
命名应用名称应用名称
then
然后
all right then
那好吧
then we need to confirm so I guess we
然后我们需要确认，所以我猜我们
can menephta
可以吗
as is right now here at that point we
就像现在在这里
get a mono that's empty right it would
得到一个空的单声道吧
it would complete but we'd have to
它会完成，但我们必须
listen to it by looking at they do one
看着他们听一听
terminate for example a publisher and I
例如终止出版商，而我
want to I want to keep the processing
想要我想要继续处理
going so instead of terminating here
这样，而不是在这里终止
with an empty void based mono I want to
与一个空的基于空的单声道我想
actually the switch again so I'm just
实际上是再次切换，所以我只是
gonna return a you know a boolean true
要返回一个你知道布尔值是真的
to confirm that everything is as we
确认一切都和我们一样
expect the true is nice because if we
期望真实是好的，因为如果我们
don't have the truly notice thing is
没有真正注意到的事情是
wrong it's also nice because that it's
对，这也很好，因为
an it's a value that a publisher can
这是发布商可以拥有的价值
omit and that's actually what we want in
省略，这实际上是我们想要的
order to be able to continue chaining
为了能够继续链接
this with other processing so bouillon
这个和其他的肉汤一起加工
ma no letter return a model of bullion
马无信退还金银模型
right all right turn there we are good
好吧好吧转弯那里我们很好
so there's our mono and we can continue
所以有我们的单声道，我们可以继续
chaining so bind service to application
链接，因此将服务绑定到应用程序
so we're gonna say push the application
所以我们要说推送应用程序
then bind the service instance to the
然后将服务实例绑定到
application then now we need to restart
应用程序，那么现在我们需要重新启动
the service right so restart the
服务正确，所以重新启动
application rather so restart
应用程序，所以重新启动
application app name and here this is
应用程序名称，这是
pretty easy as well so create that
也很容易，所以创建
method it's gonna be a mono of boolean
方法，它将是布尔值的单声道
just as before all right I'm going to
就像以前一样，我要去
say we turn operations dots applications
说我们转向运营点应用
dot we start we start the application
点，我们启动，我们启动应用程序
request builder dot name this is the the
请求构建器点名称，这是
app name so here we are done build and
应用名称，因此在这里我们完成了构建和
then return mono dot just the boolean
然后返回布尔值的单点
true alright same as before so now we
真的和以前一样好，现在我们
can change that again so we're gonna say
可以再次改变它，所以我们要说
create the service if it's missing then
如果缺少该服务，则创建该服务
public push the application then bind
公开推送应用程序然后绑定
the application of the service instance
服务实例的应用
then restart the application and then
然后重新启动应用程序，然后
finally once we have a in this case this
最终一旦我们有一个在这种情况下
will be you know the last true value we
你会知道我们最后的真实价值吗
received once right we don't actually
收到一次，我们实际上并没有
care but that's what that's what that's
关心，但这就是那就是那
going to be that's going to be the
将会是
output emitted value from this stage in
从此阶段输出的发射值
the pipeline right and so we can
管道正确，所以我们可以
actually just call it X in other
实际上只是在其他地方称它为X
languages like like Scala you can do
可以像Scala这样的语言
underscore for example so you know X we
例如下划线，那么您知道X我们
can't do that but X is fine
无法做到这一点，但X可以
all right and I guess that's it I guess
好吧，我想就是这样
that's kind of an interesting little
有点有趣
flow so let's go ahead and run this and
流程，让我们继续运行并
see what we get okay first of all let's
首先看看我们还好吧，让我们
go ahead and see if a CF s CF team s- f
继续前进，看看CF的CF团队s- f
st my sequel so i'm going to delete that
我的续集，所以我要删除它
all right and now this should deploy
好的，现在应该部署
this application it should it should
此应用程序应该
deploy two instances the application and
部署两个实例的应用程序和
remember what's gonna happen it's gonna
记住会发生什么
take that jar it's gonna take it - it's
把那个罐子拿走-是的
gonna push the application to the
会将应用程序推送到
platform but it's not going to start you
平台，但不会开始
know the platform is gonna see the
知道平台会看到
incoming jar and it's gonna create a
传入的罐子，它将创建一个
container out of that jar and it's gonna
从那个罐子里拿出来的容器
lay down a filesystem it has everything
放下一个文件系统，它拥有一切
that's needed to read to run that
需要阅读才能运行该程序
application including in this case a jdk
在这种情况下包括jdk的应用程序
a JVM it's going to sort of you know
一个JVM，你会知道
inspect the incoming artifacts so don't
检查传入的工件，所以不要
know that it's a java application it's a
知道这是一个Java应用程序
dot jar if we were to upload a dot waar
点瓶，如果我们要上传点波形
it would download apache tomcat and if
它将下载apache tomcat，如果
it were Ruby and rails or you know that
那是Ruby和rails，或者你知道
or whatever it would um it would do the
或它会做的任何事情
right thing there as well right but in
正确的东西在那里，但是在
this case is the dot jar it's gonna be
这种情况是点罐子
just Java jar so it's gonna download JDK
只是Java jar，所以它将下载JDK
in this case it's gonna be JDK 8 or
在这种情况下，它将是JDK 8或
whatever the latest and greatest is
无论最新和最伟大的是什么
supported by default on the hosted
默认情况下在托管上受支持
platform and by the way there is I think
平台，顺便说一句，我认为
preliminary support for using Java 9 by
对使用Java 9的初步支持
overwriting the build pack and that is
覆盖构建包，那就是
something that we could have specified
我们可以指定的东西
here if we want to be very specific now
如果我们现在想非常具体
it's gonna do all that first it's gonna
首先要做所有的事情
create a file system it's gonna turn
创建一个文件系统
that into a container which it'll then
把它放进一个容器里
start if we tell it to and it'll
如果我们告诉它，它将开始
provision it and you know
供应它，你知道
deployed across the cluster so in this
部署在整个集群中
case it took us 20 sorry 73 millisecond
案件花了我们20抱歉73毫秒
so 73 seconds and seventy-three point
所以73秒和73点
six seconds if we look at this you can
六秒钟，如果我们看着这个，你可以
see ft my sequel is there it's been
看我的续集在那儿吗
bound to this app called st app SF or CF
绑定到名为st app SF或CF的此应用程序
a that's the apps command there's the
这是apps命令，
app if we go to you know st apps like
应用，如果我们去找你，你会知道像
that high spring tips alright so those
好Spring 的提示好吧，那些
are deployed cloud fund application now
现在已部署云资金应用程序
what we have done here is we've you know
我们在这里所做的是我们知道
we've gotta mated something that you
我们必须交配一些你
could do in four or five lines of bash
可以进行四到五行打击
with just a mere 130 or so kind of Java
仅用130种左右的Java
code now is this better well you know we
现在的代码会更好，你知道我们
can disagree or we can have the
可以不同意或者我们可以
discussion about that certainly but the
当然可以讨论，但是
point is this is more maintainable right
关键是这是更容易维护的权利
you can look at this code you can change
你可以看一下这段代码，你可以改变
it you can do more interactive things
你可以做更多互动的事情
with it it's faster you can also do much
有了它，您也可以做很多事
more complex things you can arrange for
您可以安排的更复杂的事情
example to to have certain things happen
发生某些事情的例子
you can interrogate the state and store
您可以询问状态并存储
things and variables in a much more
事物和变量更多
natural way than you might with with
一种自然的方式
bash and you can build tools on this
bash，您可以在此基础上构建工具
right there's no reason you couldn't
对，没有理由你不能
build your whole continuous delivery
建立整个连续交付
pipeline and then program it right this
管道，然后对此进行编程
is no you're not you're not moving
不，你不是，你不动
infrastructure around you're you you're
您周围的基础设施就是您
using API is to create api's so this
使用API​​是为了创建api，因此
gives you a lot of power like I said I
就像我说的那样给你很大的力量
like the idea of having a shippable
像拥有可运送物品的想法
spring shell based application you you
基于Spring Shell的应用程序
know you can put it in a continuous
知道你可以把它连续
delivery pipeline right you can say - -
您可以说交付管道正确--
replicas equals five whatever and then
副本等于五，然后
point it to the jar and then they'll do
将其指向罐子，然后他们会做
the rest it knows exactly what's
其余的它确切地知道是什么
required to make sure that this thing is
需要确保这个东西是
running correctly and to tried-and-true
正确运行并经过反复试验
proven solution and you can also use
经过验证的解决方案，您也可以使用
this in your smoke test you know to to
这在你的烟雾测试中，你知道要
make sure that your end-to-end pieces
确保端到端的作品
are up and running this is a very simple
启动并运行这是非常简单的
example but as you saw the API has a lot
例子，但是如您所见，API有很多
of power you can you can do everything
力量，您可以做所有事情
you could do from the CF command line
您可以从CF命令行执行
and in some cases even more right
在某些情况下甚至更正确
because you can get at the low-level
因为你可以在低层次
api's then are used in aggregate from
然后将api用于聚合
the CF CLI um all right well with that
CF CLI很好
thanks so much for watching and we'll
非常感谢您的收看，我们会
see you next time
下次见
you
您